<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Virtual Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="list_button">List</string>
    <string name="grid_button">Grid</string>
    <string name="intent_picker">Intent Picker</string>
    <string name="menu_resource">Inflating a Menu</string>
    <string name="document">Document</string>
    <string name="spreadsheet">Spreadsheet</string>
    <string name="folder">Folder</string>
    <string name="upload_photos">Upload photos or videos</string>
    <string name="use_camera">Use camera</string>
    <string name="share_some_text">Share some text!</string>
    <string name="image_picker">Image picker</string>
    <string name="show">Show</string>
    <string name="reopen">Reopen as other type</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_fragment">BottomSheet Fragment</string>

    <string name="BackDropBottomSheetBehavior">co.com.parsoniisolutions.custombottomsheetbehavior.lib.BackdropBottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="BottomSheetBehaviorGoogleMapsLike">co.com.parsoniisolutions.custombottomsheetbehavior.lib.BottomSheetBehaviorGoogleMapsLike</string>
    <string name="ScrollAwareFABBehavior">co.com.parsoniisolutions.custombottomsheetbehavior.lib.ScrollAwareFABBehavior</string>
    <string name="MergedAppBarLayoutBehavior">co.com.parsoniisolutions.custombottomsheetbehavior.lib.MergedAppBarLayoutBehavior</string>
    <string name="ScrollingAppBarLayoutBehavior">co.com.parsoniisolutions.custombottomsheetbehavior.lib.ScrollingAppBarLayoutBehavior</string>

    <string name="key_binding_default_toolbar_name">Modal-Toolbar-Title</string>
    <string name="dummy_text">Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); </string>


    <!-- intro -->

        <string name="title_menu_github">View on GitHub</string>
        <string name="title_menu_reset_first_start">Reset "First start" flag</string>

        <string name="label_options">Options:</string>
        <string name="label_option_fullscreen">Enable fullscreen</string>
        <string name="label_option_scrollable">Scrollable slides</string>
        <string name="label_option_custom_fragments">Enable custom fragments</string>
        <string name="label_option_permissions">Enable permission request</string>
        <string name="label_option_show_back">Show back button</string>
        <string name="label_option_show_next">Show next button</string>
        <string name="label_option_skip_enabled">Enable skip button</string>
        <string name="label_option_finish_enabled">Enable finish button</string>
        <string name="label_option_get_started_enabled">Enable \"Get Started\" button</string>
        <string name="label_start_intro">Start intro</string>
        <string name="label_or">or</string>
        <string name="label_demos">Demos: </string>
        <string name="label_start_canteen">\"Canteen\" intro</string>
        <string name="label_start_splash">Splash screen</string>

        <string name="title_material_metaphor">Material is the metaphor</string>
        <string name="title_material_bold">This is title_material_bold in strings.xml</string>
        <string name="title_material_motion">Motion provides meaning</string>
        <string name="title_material_shadow">Light and shadow</string>

        <string name="description_material_metaphor">A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion. The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.</string>
        <string name="description_material_bold">The foundational elements of print-based design – typography, grids, space, scale, color, and use of imagery – guide visual treatments.</string>
        <string name="description_material_motion">Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.</string>
        <string name="description_material_shadow">Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.</string>

        <string name="title_permissions">Requesting permissions was never easier.</string>
        <string name="description_permissions">This app needs the camera and storage permission.\nIt\'s only to show how permission requests work in this library and we won\'t do anything with the granted permissions.</string>
        <string name="label_grant_permissions">Please grant the permissions before proceeding.</string>

        <string name="label_button_cta">Click me!</string>
        <string name="toast_button_cta">Hey, that\'s how custom CTA buttons work in material-intro!</string>

        <string name="title_fragment_login">This is a custom fragment.</string>
        <string name="hint_fake_username">Fake username</string>
        <string name="hint_fake_password">Fake password</string>
        <string name="label_fake_login">Fake login</string>
        <string name="label_fake_login_loading">Loading…</string>
        <string name="label_fake_login_success">Logged in ☺</string>
        <string name="label_fake_login_success_message">Successfully faked login.</string>
        <string name="label_fill_out_form">Please choose at least one major you are interested in</string>

        <string name="title_fragment_custom">Take off!</string>

        <string name="label_activity_finish">Nothing here…\n…just a demo how to create a splash screen intro.</string>

        <string name="title_canteen_intro1" translatable="false">Menus right on your screen</string>
        <string name="title_canteen_intro2" translatable="false">Cash on delivery</string>
        <string name="title_canteen_intro3" translatable="false">Choose what you like</string>
        <string name="description_canteen_intro1" translatable="false">Looking for something to eat? Just browse the feed wherever you are.</string>
        <string name="description_canteen_intro2" translatable="false">Order and we\'ll deliver the menu right in front of your door.</string>
        <string name="description_canteen_intro3" translatable="false">Bookmark a menu you wanted to save and keep track of its status whether it\'s available or not.</string>
        <string name="label_button_cta_canteen_intro" translatable="false">Get started</string>

    <string name="Upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="Error">Error</string>
    <string name="Complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="IndeterminateProgressSample">Indeterminate Progress Sample</string>
    <string name="IntegerProgressSample">Integer Progress Sample</string>
    <string name="StateChangeSample">State Change Sample</string>
    <string name="ProgressPaddingSample">Progress Padding Sample</string>
    <string name="CustomSelectorSample">Custom Selector Sample</string>

    <string name="introductionMessage">Welcome to the Jack Baskin School of Engineering at UC Santa Cruz. We will show you a wide variety of research labs, club activities, and instructional labs that you may soon become a part of based on what majors you are interested in. Please select the major(s) that you are interested in studying, and we\'ll show you the points of interest related to that major. You can select other majors to see what other fields of study have to offer as well.</string>

    <string name="be105Desciption">\'BE105 and BE109 are two of the few 24-hour computer labs on campus. Most Computer Science and Computer Engineering students will spend their time here during lab sections for their lower-division Computer Science and Computer Engineering courses. Here students learn how to access the UNIX servers hosted by the School of Engineering so they can access their work remotely. In addition, classes such as robot automation and assembly language are held here.\'</string>

    <string name="gameLabDescription">\'The Game Lab is among the most distinctive teaching labs at UC Santa Cruz. Here, undergraduate game majors work in teams of 4 to 15 students to create a substantial computer game over their entire senior year. Game Lab games have won awards at game festivals such as IndieCade and the Google Play Indie Games awards, and are publicly released on platforms such as Itch.io, the Apple App Store, and the Google Play Store. The lab features high end computer workstations with VR-capable graphics cards and dual monitors, virtual reality headsets, game prototyping supplies, a sound studio, an extensive library of books on game topics, and multiple team meeting spaces.\'</string>
    <string name="mechatronicsDescription">\'BE115 is home to CMPE118: Introduction to Mechatronics. In this class teams of 3 to 4 students must build a fully autonomous robot from the ground up in 5 weeks meaning that once the power switch is on, the robot must function on its own. The first five weeks students learn about components that are needed to build the robot, such as amplifiers, infrared sensors, bump sensors, and so on. The rest of the quarter they focus on building a complete robot. At the end of the quarter there’s a competition. Previous examples include a competition based on Ender\’s Game, where the robot had to navigate around stars and find the enemys home beacon. Also, robots scored points every time it was hit by an enemy\’s ping-pong ball.\'</string>
    <string name="ee101Description">\'The circuits lab (Baskin 150) is used for beginning instruction in analog electronics, both for EE 101/L (Circuits) and BME 51AB (Applied Electronics for Bioengineers). The class shown here is one section of BME 51A, doing their first amplifier lab: building an instrumentation amplifier for a pressure sensor for measuring air pressure in a blood-pressure cuff. All the bioengineering concentrations are required to complete BME 51, as it provides a relatively quick way to gain practical engineering design experience and to understand the basics of interfacing biological systems to computers.\'</string>
    <string name="graduateAdvisingDescription">\'The BSOE Graduate Advising office is available to help students, staff, and faculty with academic policy pertaining to graduate education at UCSC. This unit is responsible for processing petitions, TA assignments, committee nominations, advancement to candidacy, intake of theses and dissertations, conducting the degree checks to award all master’s and doctoral degrees, graduate, and navigating academic performance and progress.\n\nHow To Meet With a Graduate Advisor: Advisors are available for both drop-in advising and appointments and are located in Oakes Academic Building, Room 221.\n\nIf you anticipate needing more than 10 minutes with an advisor, we recommend making an appointment. You can schedule an appointment by visiting the Contacts &amp; Hours page and select Schedule an Appointment with the advisor for your program. When visiting the Graduate Advising Office, you will be asked to sign in with your name, the advisor you wish to see, and if it is a scheduled or drop-in appointment.\n\nDrop-In advising hours are limited, so please plan ahead as we can fill up quickly during peak times in the quarter. Advising By Email: When emailing the BSOE Advising staff please email from your UCSC email account an\n\n include your name, program, student ID and your question. Please do not email advisors to request an appointment.  We are happy to help with many things, but it is the student’s responsibility to come prepared. Please always refer to the Graduate Advising website as answers to many of your questions can be found here. We look forward to meeting with you soon!\'</string>
    <string name="graduateHousingDescription">\'Graduate Student Housing is an intimate community housing just 82 students, and is home to a diverse group, including students from all over the United States and the world. The apartments are set in a beautifully landscaped natural environment conveniently located adjacent to Science Hill, home to many of UCSCs main academic facilities. Each apartment has four single bedrooms, living room, kitchen, dining room, and bathroom. Ground floor apartments have decks, while upper apartments have private balconies.\'</string>

    <string name="danserDescription">\'DANSER is the Dynamics, Autonomous Navigation, Surface Engineering and Robotics Lab at University of California, Santa Cruz. Our lab builds structurally compliant robots for applications including exosuits, exoskeletons, manipulators, prosthetics, and rovers. Tensegrity is a design principle that features compression elements suspended within a network of tension elements. This fusion results in a hybrid soft-rigid structure that easily complies with external stresses by distributing loads throughout the entire tension network. This paradigm is particularly useful for developing robots that mimic musculoskeletal kinematics and dynamics. We have chosen to apply these ideas to our own biomechanically-oriented projects\'</string>
    <string name="opticsLabDescription">\'The main research theme in our group is single particle optics. We develop new, highly sensitive methods to study single particles with optical methods. We use these and other established techniques to gain new understanding of these particles and light-matter interactions in general. Due to the versatility of optical methods, we can investigate different types of particles. Our current focus areas are: single biomolecules (Integrated Optofluidics), single nanomagnets (Nano-magneto-optics), and single photons (Atomic spectroscopy on a chip).\n\nWe are affiliated with the California Institute for Quantitative Biomedical Research (QB3), the Center for Biomolecular Science and Engineering (CBSE), and the Storage Systems Research Center (SSRC). Professor Schmidt directs the W.M. Keck Center for Nanoscale Optofluidics, whose mission is to incorporate nanoscale features in optofluidic devices to enable new studies of bioparticles and biological processes.\'</string>

    <string name="be301Description">\'BE301A – Computer Networks Lab: This lab is used by the University’s Computer Networking and Electrical Engineering courses. Students in these courses receive hands-on experience with real-world networking equipment and concepts to prepare them for careers as network engineers. They use software such as Wireshark to observe packets as they travel through a computer network to understand how communication between routers, switches, and computers occurs on Local Area Networks as well as the Internet. Additionally, students are introduced to emerging concepts, such as Software Defined Networking, to prepare them for the Internet of the future.\'</string>
    <string name="computationalGenomicsDescription">\'Our research is currently focused on:  Building technology to connect the institutional silos where genome information is now isolated by forging and implementing interoperable standards. We are proud members of the Global Alliance for Genomics and Health, comparing the history of vertebrate genomes. Want to reconstruct a 65-million-year-old genome from the genomes of its descendants? Talk to us! We love the Genome 10K, a project to sequence 10,000 vertebrate genomes using next-next generation sequencing technology to create more complete, accurate and phased genomes and making it easy to discover and share portable, reproducible, and scalable genomic workflows. We analyze massive genomic datasets using the cloud and build a human reference genome structure that contains all common variation as a universal basis for genomics. We are also completing the library of human and mouse RNAs.\'</string>

    <string name="mepDescription"></string>
    <string name="nanoporeLabDescription"></string>
    <string name="humanGenomeDescription"></string>
    <string name="computerVisionDescription"></string>

    <!-- Lab Descriptions plus Introduciton
    <string name="introductionMessage">Welcome to the Jack Baskin School of Engineering at UC Santa Cruz. We will show you a wide variety of research labs, club activities, and instructional labs that you may soon become a part of based on what majors you are interested in. Please select the major(s) that you are interested in studying, and we'll show you the points of interest related to that major. You can select other majors to see what other fields of study have to offer as well.</string>
    <string name=""></string>
    <string name=""></string>
    <string name=""></string>
    <string name=""></string>
be105Desciption
gameLabDescription
mechatronicsDescription
ee101Description
graduateAdvisingDescription
graduateHousingDescription
    -->
    <array name="sample_list">
        <item>@string/IndeterminateProgressSample</item>
        <item>@string/IntegerProgressSample</item>
        <item>@string/StateChangeSample</item>
        <item>@string/ProgressPaddingSample</item>
        <item>@string/CustomSelectorSample</item>
    </array>

</resources>
